RPGViewer 3.0 by Van

Install:
First, you need to download and install Visual C++ 2012 Redistributable Package (http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=30679)
Besides RPGViewer, don't forget to download RPGViewerSupportFile.
After extracting RPGViewer, you need to extract RPGViewerSupportFile to the same location.

DISCLAIMER:
The software is provided as is. The author is not responsible for any damage by the software. Please backup your data if possible.
Import and export functionality provided in the software are for research purpose only.
The resources extracted by the software are owned by the corresponding owner. You SHOULD NOT redistribute them without the permission of the owner.

Introduction:
1. View Picture
Open the game using "File" menu. If it is the first time you open the game, RPGViewer will prompt you for the path of the game. Normally, you can choose the path which contains the executable of the game.
After opening the game, you can navigate the pictures in it using "View" menu or toolbar.
If any error occured when loading the picture, RPGViewer will show the error message in the status bar.
2. Search
You can search the picture by their name (if they have name).
Search support fuzzy, case sensitive and regular expression.
3. Export  Picture (support bmp, jpg, png and mng format. Sango SHP format is supported, too)
RPGViewer support three types of export:
a. Current Frame
Export the current displaying frame
b. Current Picture
Export all the frames in the picture.
If the picture contains only one frame, it is the same as "Current Frame".
c. All Pictures
Export all pictures
4. Import Picture (support bmp, gif, jpg and png format)
You can import the pictures (if supported) using bmp or png (which support transparent color and alpha-channel) format.
(Notice: "Import" here only turn on a replacement flag, no actual replacement happens)
If you want to undo the replacement, simply use "Restore" in the "Import" menu
After finish importing, you can use "Save" in the "Import" menu to save the changes.
5. View Archive
You can view the files in the archive or export them. Some types of archive support replacement.